amli.com 2019-07-22

# AMLI.com - Privacy Policy

|  | 

**AMLI Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date:** 8.24.18

 **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Thank you for visiting the AMLI Residential (“ **AMLI** ”) website (including any AMLI-branded and affiliated websites that are both directly linked from this website and display a link to this Privacy Policy, the “ **Websites** ”). Your privacy is important to us. To help you better understand our privacy practices, we provide this Privacy Policy, which explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to you or any other person (via email or otherwise), by posting changes on the Websites. We encourage you to check back and review this Privacy Policy from time to time to remain fully informed of our commitments. The amended Privacy Policy will be effective upon posting on the Websites, so when you use the Websites or provide us with Personal Information (as defined below), you indicate your consent to this Privacy Policy as modified from time to time, including your consent to our (and third parties on our behalf) collection and use of Personal Information. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices regarding information collected from you, or that you provide to us or third parties on our behalf, including, but not limited to, through the Websites. If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to access or use the Websites and you must disconnect from and not use the Websites. 

**The Information We May Collect**

1\. Traffic Data

We automatically track and collect general log information when you visit the Websites, including but not limited to your IP address, domain server, operating system, and type of web browser as well as the pages you visit (“Traffic Data”). Traffic Data may not personally identify you, but is helpful for marketing purposes and for improving your experience on the Websites. We use the Traffic Data to report aggregated activity on the Websites and to better understand the needs of our users so we can make informed decisions regarding the content and design of the Websites. It helps us: 

•to estimate our audience size and usage pattern;

•to learn what information is of most and least interest;

•to speed up your searches; and

•to learn of any possible performance problems on the Websites.

We may collect Traffic Data through various methods including, but not limited to, cookies (which are text files sent to your web browser and stored on your hard disk, to enable us to provide you with a more individualized experience on the Websites and delivery of information), IP addresses, and transparent GIFs or pixel tags (which are small graphic files that allow us to monitor the use of the Websites and our email communications). We may also use Traffic Data, including tracking cookies and retargeting marketing cookies, to provide you with AMLI-related advertising, including via our third-party advertising partners, and share with our analytics providers (as further described below). 

2\. Personal Information

You may provide us (or a third party on our behalf) with personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) when you use the Websites (e.g., when you sign up for an account, request a quote, complete a survey, fill out a lease application, request information or a service, sign up for a mailing list, sign up to receive AMLI text alerts, provide feedback, or apply for an employment listing) or provide us with such Personal Information offline (e.g., fill out a paper lease application offline). The types of Personal Information collected on the Websites may include, but are not limited to: 

  * Name

  * Address  

  * E-mail address

  * Phone number

  * Gender

  * Social security number

  * Responses to survey questions

  * Responses to lease application questions

  * Credit card number

  * Employment history

  * Bank account number

In addition, if you use the mobile version of the Websites (the “Mobile Site”), the types of Personal Information collected on the Mobile Site may include, but are not limited to:

  * Name

  * E-mail address

  * Mobile phone number

  * Geo-location information

  * Web browsing history

In addition, if you sign up to receive AMLI text alerts, the types of Personal Information obtained from you in connection with AMLI’s text alerts service may include, but are not limited to:

  * Mobile phone number

  * Your carrier's name

  * Date, time and content of your messages and other information that you may provide

Note your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data from your texts and messaging usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

 **How We Use Personal Information**

We may use and/or disclose Personal Information for the following reasons: 

  * We may use your contact information, including your e-mail address and phone number, to communicate with you (e.g., to notify you of special offers or programs you might find of interest, to respond to your inquiries, comments and suggestions, and to contact you otherwise when necessary).

  * We may share or use your Personal Information to process your lease application or employment application, including verifying statements made on your application (e.g., rental, credit and employment history), performing background and credit checks, reviewing your lease for renewal, and enforcing your lease obligations.

  * We use the information you provide about someone else when forwarding a job listing to send that listing and to confirm delivery.

  * We may use your contact information to provide order status and order tracking information.

  * We may use the content of your submissions on the Website for promotional or marketing purposes.

  * We may use and share certain information (e.g., excluding name, address, email address or telephone number, but including but not limited to geo-location information and Traffic Data) and aggregate information to better design, operate and improve the Website and our services and to share with our advertising partners. 

  * If you choose to register or receive products or materials from us, or to otherwise give us Personal Information, we may store some or all of that Personal Information and use it for marketing research and marketing purposes.

  * We may provide Personal Information to AMLI’s affiliates or third parties in connection with the business purposes of AMLI or the Websites, including, without limitation, to provide services to you.

  * We reserve the right to share any Personal Information in the event of a criminal investigation or suspected illegal activity, or as required by law or regulation, or as requested by government or regulatory authorities, or to avoid liability, or to protect our rights or property. 

  * We may share Personal Information in connection with an acquisition, merger, restructuring, sale or other transfer involving all or any portion of AMLI or the business associated with the Websites.

  * We may share Personal Information for other business purposes of AMLI.

 **Children's Privacy**

Except with respect to collection of specific data required to determine unit occupancy within our online leasing process, we do not collect information on the Websites from those we know are under 13, and the registration page for the Websites requires visitors wishing to become Website registrants to be at least 18 years of age. No part of the Websites is structured to attract anyone under 13. By using the Websites, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**

1\. General

The Websites may offer links to third party websites that may have information policies and practices different from ours (e.g., utility connection websites, rent easy-pay websites, or any AMLI-branded websites that are operated by third parties and do not link to this Privacy Policy). The fact that we have provided a link to a site is NOT an endorsement, authorization, sponsorship, or affiliation by us with respect to such website, its owners, or its providers. We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of any third party websites. 

2\. Locator Services

If you found us through a locator service, please be aware that locator services are independent contractors and are not our employees or agents, even though they may initially process rental applications and fill out lease forms. You should require any locator services you use to furnish you their own privacy policies. 

**Advertising and Opt-Out**

Our third-party advertising partners may use certain information about your visits (e.g., excluding name, address, email address or telephone number, but including but not limited to geo-location information and Traffic Data) to this and other websites, mobile websites and/or mobile applications across your various devices, in order to provide content and advertisements about AMLI to you across those various devices. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices with respect to it, please: (1) visit the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page (currently available at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>) or the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page (currently available at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>) to learn how to opt out of having your information collected in browsers for ad serving purposes; and (2) download the Ghostery Ad Control application, available for iOS and Android, to learn how to opt out of having your information collected in mobile apps.

 **Non-U.S. Residents**

We provide services within United States. We do not provide services in the European Union. If you reside in the European Union and believe you have mistakenly entered information in our site and wish to have that data deleted, we will honor that request to the extent allowed by applicable law. Please forward any such request here: data-optout@amli.com .

If you provide Personal Information to us, it may be transferred to and processed on computers in the U.S. and other countries. Do not provide Personal Information to us if you do not want this information to be transferred to the United States or to other countries, or if the laws in your country restrict these types of transfers. Your provision of Personal Information to us will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your provision of Personal Information to us through the Website means that you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

**Website Security**

We use reasonable security safeguards to protect the Personal Information that we collect from unauthorized access. However, due to the design of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. While no one can guarantee against identity theft or the misuse of personal information, protecting the information you provide us is a high priority to our company and staff. If you ever have concerns about this issue, please feel free to share them with us. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

For purposes of California residents, this Privacy Policy pertains to all information collected online, including through the Websites. California law permits customers of AMLI who are California residents to request certain information regarding AMLI’s disclosure of personal data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us through the information provided in the “How to Contact Us” section below. 

**California Do Not Track Disclosures**

Certain web browsers may include settings that allow you to provide “do not track” (DNT) signals to the websites you visit. However, DNT is an evolving technology that currently lacks finalized industry protocols and standards. As such, the Websites do not currently respond to DNT signals, but instead adhere to the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy. For more information about DNT, please visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

When you visit the Websites, our third-party advertising partners, social media providers (e.g., Facebook, Pinterest) and analytics providers (e.g., Google Analytics) may collect information about your online activity on the Websites and on third-party websites. These providers may set web tracking tools (e.g., cookies and web beacons) to collect non-personally identifiable information regarding your online activity (e.g., Traffic Data). In addition, our advertising partners may use this information to deliver advertisements to you when you visit third-party websites within their networks. Please see the “Advertising” section above for more information, including how to opt-out.

 **Google Analytics**

The Websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the Websites analyze how users use the Websites. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Websites (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Websites, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Websites. By using the Websites, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. More information about Google Analytics and how you may opt-out is available [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).  

 **Your Choice to Share Information**

If you would prefer that we not share your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes or would like to update your Personal Information, please contact us through the information provided in the “How to Contact Us” section below. 

**E-Mail Consent**

When you provide Personal Information to us through the Websites, you are consenting to receive email from us, which may include, but is not limited to, password requests, information relating to your leasing or employment application, and information you request. In addition, you may receive commercial email messages from us, including marketing announcements or new job opportunities. If you do not wish to receive future commercial email messages from us, you may opt out of receiving such commercial email messages by following the link and instructions provided to you in such email messages. This opt out applies to commercial email messages only. If you are an AMLI resident, you consent to receive and we may still send you email regarding operational matters pertaining to your apartment, the AMLI community in which your apartment is located or your lease with us. If you are a leasing or employment applicant, you consent to receive and we may still send you email regarding your application process. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [webmaster@amli.com](mailto:webmaster@amli.com).
